Ahay -  by Of Monsters and Men
I know that I'm wrong
And now we're both sitting in silence
But if it's alright
I'll wrap myself around your cold shoulder
You think you know me
But do you really?
Something you do, something you say
Oh, we don't talk about it
You think you know me
But do you really?
There's somethin' 'bout you
Somethin' 'bout you
(We don't talk about it)
A bull without horns
Said nothing, so how come I'm blushing?
And though you are warm
The cold lingers on the tip of your fingers
You think you know me
But do you really?
Something you do, something you say
Oh, we don't talk about it
You think you know me
But do you really?
There's somethin' 'bout you
Somethin' 'bout you
Oh, you couldn't change this mountain
You've got me out chasing the sound but I just hear fractions
You've got me out facing the sun but I just need direction
You think you know me
But do you really?
Something you do, something you say
Oh, we don't talk about it
You think you know me
But do you really? (Hey)
There's somethin' 'bout you
Somethin' 'bout you
(We don't talk about it)